Mustafa Alsaeedi

850B Forest St, Buford, GA 30518 (678) 437-2019/ mustafa.f.alsaeedi@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/MustafaAlsaeedi

OBJECTIVE

I have over 7 years' experience working in a business environment. I have gained diverse experiences through the people with whom I've worked. I enjoy developing websites and coding, which will help me follow my passion for accounting by understanding the software that I will be using as an accountant.

EDUCATION

Georgia State University – J Mark Robinson College of Business

Jan 2018 - Dec 2019

Bachelors of Business Administration in Accounting

Bachelors of Business Administration in Computer Information Systems

Georgia State University – Perimeter College

Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

Associate of Science in Business Administration

EXPERIENCE

Cox Communications

Dunwoody, GA

Portfolio Delivery - Co-op

Aug 2018 - Current

- Maintenance of Cox.com financials and analysis of data across each Program team (i.e. updating/maintaining monthly forecasts in the team forecast tool and entering dollars into necessary Project Management Tools).
- Identification of upcoming projects impacting the Cox.com Program by attending weekly project calls.
- Scheduling and support of the Quarterly Release Planning review(s) with Business/Technology Stakeholders.
- Initiated knowledge management project for senior leaders and outside teams who request information on weekly bases.
- Developed PHP application to track Cox.com residential customers feedback and send the data to specific teams through an automated emails.

Friends of Refugees – Refugee Career Hub Operation Specialist

Clarkston, GA

April 2017 – May 2019

- Developing RCH program website, including approximately 15 pages.
- Compiling and ordering supplies from weekly of technology and program supplies.
- Being on call to coordinate and/or perform software installations, diagnostics, and repairs as well as managing hardware, and information system.
- Reporting progress of computer system upgrades and new technology projects.
- Creating weekly reports to staff regarding office computer use/problems.
- Recording program updates in a monthly report document including in-kind donations report.

CSM Bakery Solutions

Tucker, GA

Warehouse Lead February 2014 – June 2015

Supervised a team of 3 forklift drivers; responsible for receiving, put away, and inventory delivery to production lines.

- During tenure as Lead:
 - Achieved zero production line down time as a result of correct and timely inventory deliveries.
 - Met zero harm targets, experiencing no safety incidents or violations.
- Promoted to warehouse lead after four months as certified forklift operator.

- Maintained database inventory with scanner, ensuring all supplies were accounted for.
- Conducted audits and root cause analysis of inventory discrepancies and took corrective action.

CORE QUALIFICATION

- QuickBooks software Knowledge
- Develop websites using HTML, CSS, PHP, and JS
- Java Knowledge
- Microsoft Excel/Tableau

LANGUAGE

- English, fluent
- Arabic, native